redz.com 2008-02-25

# RedZee Privacy Policy

**RedZee Privacy Policy**

This website (the "www.RedZee.com") is owned and operated by RedZee Search Inc. RedZee (collectively, "RedZee" or "we") are committed to respecting your online privacy and recognize your need for appropriate protection and management of any personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") you share with us. RedZee has established this Privacy Policy to let you know what information we may collect from you on the site and how we may use that information. Please take a moment to review the terms of our Privacy Policy. By using the Site (including RedZee's “RedZee” search engine and any other services offered on the Site), you agree to accept the terms of our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the site or our services. This Privacy Policy applies only to information that we collect on the site (or otherwise through our search engine) and does not apply to information which we may collect by other means. 

Personal Information Information We May Collect

Personal Information means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, a home or other physical address and an email address. In general, you can visit the Site and use its search engine and other features without telling us who you are or revealing any Personal Information about yourself. However, in order to access certain information, services or features contained on the Site, we may require you to provide Personal Information. For example, we will collect certain Personal Information if you choose to subscribe to our mailing list or send questions or comments to us via e-mail.

How We May Use Your Information

Some of our web pages utilize "cookies" and other tracking technologies. A cookie is a small text file that a website transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies may be used, for example, to collect information about website activity. Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them. You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser. However, please be aware that some features of the Site may not function properly or may be slower if you refuse cookies. You may occasionally get cookies from our advertisers or other third parties with links on the Site. We do not control these cookies. The use of advertising cookies sent by third-party servers is standard in the Internet industry. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site.

Tracking technologies may record information such as Internet domain and host names; Internet protocol (IP) addresses; browser software and operating system types; click stream patterns; and dates and times that our Site is accessed. We do not link the information we record using tracking technologies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site.

Search Engine

When you use our search engine, we may collect certain non-personally identifiable information through the use of cookies and other tracking technologies described above. For example, when you use our search engine, we may keep track of which search terms are popular. If we display advertising to you on the Site (including the search results pages displayed after any searches you may run), such advertising may be related to the search terms you entered. RedZee may present search result links in a format that enables us to understand whether they have been followed and may monitor clicks on an individual and an aggregate basis. We use this information to understand and improve the quality of RedZee's search technology. For instance, this data helps us determine how often users are satisfied with the first result of a query and how often they proceed to later results.

Links to Other Sites

Please be aware that when you are on the site, you could be directed to other sites that are beyond our control. For example, when you use our search engine, the search results will provide links to other sites from the Site's pages that take you outside the Site. These other sites may send their own cookies to visitors, collect data or solicit Personal Information. The privacy policies of these other sites may be significantly different from this Privacy Policy. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites and cannot guarantee the security of any of your Personal Information collected there.

Security

Wherever your Personal Information may be held within RedZee or on its behalf, we intend to take reasonable and appropriate steps to protect the Personal Information that you share with us from unauthorized access or disclosure. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your Personal Information and privacy, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you disclose or transmit to us online and cannot be responsible for the theft, destruction, or inadvertent disclosure of your Personal Information.

Updating Your Information

To the extent that you do provide us with Personal Information, RedZee wishes to maintain accurate Personal Information. If we collect Personal Information from you on the Web, you may send updates and corrections about your Personal Information to privacy@RedZee.com and we will make reasonable efforts to incorporate the changes in your Personal Information that we hold as soon as practicable.

Children's Privacy

Redzee.com is not structured to attract children. Accordingly, we do not knowingly collect Personal Information from anyone under 13 years of age. If you are under the age of 13, please do not provide any Personal Information to us.

Changes to Our Privacy Policy

The terms of this Privacy Policy may change from time to time without prior notice to you, so please check this page periodically for any changes. By checking the "Last Modified" date above, you can determine if this Privacy Policy has been updated since your last visit to the Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes.

Governing Law

This Privacy Policy and the privacy practices of RedZee will be subject exclusively to the laws of the State of Florida within the United States of America. RedZee makes no representation that this Privacy Policy and such practices comply with the laws of any other country. Visitors who use the Site, the search engine or any other services offered on the Site and reside outside the United States do so on their own initiative and are responsible for compliance with local laws, if and to the extent local laws are applicable.
